DAVID ARIFALO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT



+234 814 150 5195



davidarifalo001@gmail.com



Aule Estate, Ilupeju Ondo

</>>

github.com/KVNG007

PROFILE

A committed Frontend Developer with over 2 Years experience. Highly focused with comprehensive knowledge of web development Displays ability to solve client problems via visually stimulating designs that meet the client needs and ultimately creates a good impression on the user. Eager to learn, easy going and a great team player. Passionate about creating solutions to problems and helping to add value to client business via web development.

EDUCATION

PHYSIOLOGY (B.Sc.) Federal University of Technology Akure.

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React.js

Sass

Node.is

Git

PROFESSIONAL

Team Building

Critical Thinking

Punctuality

Goal Setting

Brainstorming

Problem Solving

INTERESTS

Technology, Science, cars, Internet of things, Food, Philosophy

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Lucid Jungles | MAY 2022 - Present

Collaborate with designers, project managers, and other engineers to transform creative concepts into production realities for clients and stakeholders. Deliver high-quality, robust production code for a diverse array of projects for clients.

- Develop and style interactive web applications using React.js and Scss.
- Build and manage third-party and internal API integrations.
- Collaborate with back-end developers to improve app usability.

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Provincii Media | MAR 2022 - FEB 2023

Built and delivered technical solutions according to stakeholder business requirements. Developed, maintained, and shipped production code for client websites primarily using HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, and React.is.

- Performed quality assurance tests on various sites to ensure cross-browser compatibility and mobile responsiveness
- Performed quality assurance tests on various sites to ensure cross-browser compatibility and mobile responsiveness

INTERN FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Work Distro | JAN 2023 - MAY 2023

Collaborate with designers, project managers, and other engineers to transform creative concepts into production realities for clients and stakeholders.

- Use Markup languages like Html and JavaScript to create user friendly web pages.
- Optimize application for maximum speed.
- Get feedback from, and build solutions for users and customers.

INTERN FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ZURI TEAMS | NOV 2021 - FEB 2022

Write well designed, testable, efficient and reusable code by using best software development practices. Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical needs.

- Create website layouts and user interface using standard HTML / CSS practices
- Cooperate with other web designers to match visual intent and functionality
- Gained solid understanding of how web applications work including security, session management and development best practices.